export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your social interactions and connections?",
      "options": [
        "Fulfilling and frequent",
        "Occasionally satisfying",
        "Infrequent but satisfying",
        "Consistently lonely"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Consistently lonely"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often do you engage in social activities or spend time with friends and family?",
      "options": [
        "Regularly",
        "Occasionally",
        "Rarely",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Almost never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel a sense of isolation or disconnection from others?",
      "options": [
        "Never",
        "Rarely",
        "Sometimes",
        "Frequently"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you noticed changes in your social habits or a decrease in social interactions?",
      "options": [
        "No changes",
        "Slight changes",
        "Moderate changes",
        "Significant changes"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Significant changes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with loneliness or related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes",
        "Considering it",
        "No, not yet",
        "No, and I don't plan to"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do feelings of loneliness impact your daily life and well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact",
        "Moderate impact",
        "High impact",
        "Very high impact"
      ],
      "correctOption": "High impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you often experience a lack of emotional support or understanding from others?",
      "options": [
        "Never",
        "Rarely",
        "Sometimes",
        "Frequently"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your social isolation or loneliness?",
      "options": [
        "Never",
        "Rarely",
        "Sometimes",
        "Frequently"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing loneliness is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree",
        "Agree",
        "Neutral",
        "Disagree"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been experiencing feelings of loneliness?",
      "options": [
        "A short period",
        "Several months",
        "Years",
        "I haven't experienced feelings of loneliness"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Years"
    }
  ]
}
